jobkhojo.in 2009-06-22

# JobKhojo

| 

**Introduction**  
We, at 'Jobkhojo', are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. 

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Jobkhojo's Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. 

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site. 

**Personal Information**

'Jobkhojo' does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Jobkhojo's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Jobkhojo's policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.

**Your Consent**

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Jobkhojo's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where 'Jobkhojo' collects Personal Information on the Web.

**Information security**

  * We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.
  * At Present we are not Displaying  contact information of Jobseekers. Employers can contact jobseekers only thru our website without knowing jobseekers email ID.

Updating your information

  * We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. **Children**

  * 'Jobkhojo' will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * 'Jobkhojo' does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people (save with your consent) or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with 'Jobkhojo' under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help 'Jobkhojo' communicate with you about offers from 'Jobkhojo' and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Jobkhojo's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if 'Jobkhojo' is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, 'Jobkhojo' will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * At Present we are not Displaying  contact information of Jobseekers. Employers can contact jobseekers only thru our website without knowing jobseekers email ID. We may provide Contact information to  Users who has registered them selves as Employers to contact you directly.
  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and Rules made there under to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
'Jobkhojo' reserves the right to update, change or modify this policy at any time. The policy shall come to effect from the date of such update, change or modification. 

**Disclaimer**

 'Jobkhojo' will not be liable on account of any inaccuracy of information on this web site. It is the responsibility of the visitor to further research the information on the site. Any breach of privacy or of the information provided by the consumer to 'Jobkhojo'. to be placed on the website by technical or any other means is not the responsibility of 'Jobkhojo'. 'Jobkhojo' does not guarantee confidentiality of information provided to it by any person acquiring/using all/any information displayed on the www.jobkhojo.in website or any of its other websites / domains owned and operated by 'Jobkhojo'  
**Contact Information**  
'Jobkhojo' welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. Should there be any concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy, 'Jobkhojo' will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same.
